Guide to the Bryant Fleming plans, [ca. 1904-1937]
Fleming, Bryant plans
- Unspecified Client - Arranged by Sheet Number
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Grading, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1857
    - Grading, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1858
    - Stepping stones, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1859
    - 18" vitrified pipe catch basin, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1860
    - Grading, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1861
    - Ledge stone or field stone catch basin, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1862
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1867
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Sewage disposal, Undated (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1870
      Note:Note from J Fleming on reverse
    - Sewage disposal, Undated (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1871
  - Unspecified Location: Buffalo, NY
    - Perspective proposed improvement of terrace playgrounds and public comfort stations, 1911 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1950
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Planting plan, Undated (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 2044